Guide to the New-York Historical Society Original Building Planning & Construction Records 1848-1946 NYHS-RG 3
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Central Park West Construction: Expansion, 1925-1946; 68.48 Linear feet
  - Subseries IV.C. Plans and Drawings, 1925, 1935-1938; 60.73 Linear feet in many oversize folders, 2 flat boxes, 3 document boxes, and 5 rolls of blueprints
    For those firms with multiple folders of material, the folders are presented when possible in drawing number order.
    The bulk of the plans have been flattened and are stored in oversize folders. About 200 plans, principally by Walker & Gillette, which are duplicative of or were superseded by those in the oversize folders, were not flattened. These remain either folded in three document boxes or were placed on seven rolls. These folded or rolled plans appear in the container list after the flattened drawings. These less accessible versions of the plans should be used only if need be after referring to the flattened versions.
    The Plans and Drawings subseries includes about 1200 plans related to the 1937-1938 expansion of the Central Park West building. Most of these plans are blueprints on paper or linen, though many are also bluelined whiteprints, photographic reproductions, penciled tracings, and other formats. Although most of the plans are by the architectural firm Walker & Gillette, there is also a large number of plans by the general and sub-contractors of the project.
    Many of the plans, especially those of Walker & Gillette, are represented with multiple versions. Many of these are duplicates, but many are the earlier and later versions of particular plans that were created over the course of the project. Some of the plans are annotated with crayon markings.
    The subseries also includes plans for the expansion proposed by York & Sawyer in 1925 and in 1935-1936. None of those plans were accepted by N-YHS, which elected to use Walker & Gillette for the job. Three drawings (watercolors?) of building designs proposed by Walker & Gillette are in the subseries, including the one signed as approved by Director Alexander J. Wall.
    - Allen Automatic Inc. (Ossining, NY), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 1)
      Includes two blueprints of general layout of door 117.
    - American Bridge Co., 1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder -)
      This oversize flat box includes blueprints of index to marks and of sketch sheets for struts, beams, etc. for the first, second, and third shipments (plans F1-10, C1, EF1; F201-242; F301-356; F401-476; F501-554; F601-667; F701-799, 701A-711A; F801-832; and F901-918.
    - American Bridge Co., 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 2)
      Includes whiteprints of bracing plans (plan #E101, E102, E103, E104, E105, E105a, E201, E202, E203, E204, E205, and [E206?]).
    - American Bridge Co., 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 3)
      Includes whiteprints of bracing plans (plan #E101, E102, E103, E104, E105, E105a, and E206).
    - American Bridge Co., 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 4)
      Includes blueprints of bracing plans, grillages, anchor bolts, etc. (plan #E1, E105a, E201, E202, E203, E204, E205, E205a, E206, E301, and others).
    - American Bridge Co., 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 5)
      Includes blueprints of columns, trusses, diagonals (plan #201-208; 301-309; 401-412; 501-512; 601-613; 701-711; 801-810).
    - American Bridge Co. Folded Plans (1 of 5), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      This set of folders includes folded (unflattened) blueprints. They can be used only with assistance from the Public Services staff. This folder includes five blueprints for order H796 (sheets 1, 2, 3, and E1). Stamped as approved for strength by the consulting engineer and by Walker & Gillette.
    - American Bridge Co. Folded Plans (2 of 5), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Includes six blueprints stamped approved for strength by the consulting engineer and by Walker & Gillette (order H796: sheets E101, E102, E103, E104, E105, and E105a).
    - American Bridge Co. Folded Plans (3 of 5), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Includes seven blueprints stamped approved for strength by the consulting engineer and by Walker & Gillette (order H796: sheets E201, E202, E203, E204, E205, E205a, and E206.
    - American Bridge Co. Folded Plans (4 of 5), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Includes two blueprints stamped approved for strength by the consulting engineer and by Walker & Gillette (order H796: sheet E301). Also includes a third version of sheet E301, attached to sheet E901.
    - American Bridge Co. Folded Plans (5 of 5), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Includes one blueprint stamped approved for strength by the consulting engineer and by Walker & Gillette (order H796.X1: sheet E1).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 1)
      Includes 16 blueprints of plans for supply and exhaust risers and ducts (plan # 1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 2)
      Includes 22 blueprints of plans for supply and exhaust risers and ducts, discharge ducts, and plumbing, steam, and electrical circuits (plan # 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, and 19).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 3)
      Includes 21 blueprints of plans of supply, exhaust and discharge ducts, risers, and filters and stack casing for fans (plan # 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 27, 28, and 29).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 4)
      Includes 22 blueprints of plans for for supply and exhaust ducts and connections to risers (plan # 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, and 39).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 5)
      Includes 20 blueprints of plans for supply and exhaust ducts, locations of drains, stack bases, locations of fans in basement, fan room, and connections to discharge louvres (plan # 40, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 50, 51, and 52).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 6)
      Includes blueprints of plans for a gauge board and heaters (see also the Trane Co. folder for another version of this plan and the related Trane heater plans) and two fragmented blueprints (likely plan 19 and 29).
    - Baker, Smith & Co. (New York), 1938 (Drawer 9B-B3, Folder 7)
      Includes two whiteprints of a register (eight sheets each), stamped as final by Walker & Gillette.
    - Bishop & Babcock Manufacturing Co. (Cleveland), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 6)
      Includes plans for squirrel cage fans.
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 1)
      Includes 23 blueprints of plans concerning stairs, pintels for stairs, guard rails, wall rails, and window guards (plan # 2-1, 4-1, 7-1, 7-2, 7-3, 7-4, 7-8, 8-1, 9-1, 9-2, 9-5, and 10-1). Also includes a plan numbered as 11-1, but this appears to be a mistake; the likely number is 3-1.
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 2)
      Includes 16 blueprints of plans of wall rails, steps, ladders, platforms, and trap doors (plan # 11-1, 15-1, 15-2, 16-1, 16-1-x, 17-1, 17-2, 18-1, 19-1, 19-2, and 20-1).
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 3)
      Includes 22 blueprints of plans of loose lintels, bucks and saddles, fences for court, window grilles and guards, and access doors (plan # 21-1, 22-2, 22-3, 22-4, 22-5, 23-1, 24-1, 25-1, 25-2-x, 26-1, 27-1, 28-1, and 29-1).
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 4)
      Includes 18 blueprints of plans of ceiling sashes, W. 77th Street entrance doors and inscription panel, transom grilles, sliding doors at Central Park West entrance, and bronze frame for glass brick openings in book stack (plan # 30-1, 30-2, 30-3, 30-4, 31-1, 31-2, 31-3, 32-1, and 39-1). Also includes two unnumbered blueprints from Walker & Gillette that relate to Halback plan 30-3.
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 5)
      Includes 17 blueprints of plans of vestibule entrance, soffitt panels, bronze register grilles, steel ceiling sash, and section of bronze entrance (plan # 41-1, 41-2, 41-3, 41-4, 41-8, 42-1, and 45-1).
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 6)
      Includes six blueprints of plans of ladders in closet, bronze frames for niches in rotunda, bronze entrance at Central Park West, and bronze doors, iron frames and steel shutters (plan # 47-1, 52-1, 55-1, and 56-1).
    - C. E. Halback & Co. (Brooklyn), 1938 (Drawer 9B-B2, Folder 7)
      Includes two blueprints of plans of the rail on mezzanine steps and iron gate on W. 76th Street (plan # 60-1 and 66-1).
    - Campbell Solid Metal Window Corp. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 7)
      Includes 22 blueprints and print matter concerning windows, casements. etc.
    - Capelle, Ernest (Brooklyn), [1937?] (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 8)
      Includes two blueprints of plans for two flag poles and related sockets.
    - Chapman Metal Products Co. (New York), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 9)
      Includes four blueprints concerning doors and windows.
    - Cole Electric Products Co (Long Island City), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 10)
      Includes several whiteprints of electrical works.
    - Commercial Furniture Co., 1936 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 5)
      Includes one blueprint of a plan for the Director's table.
    - Consolidated Edison Co. (New York), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 11)
      Includes six blueprints (initial and revised) for layout of two bank transformers and switch vault below grade.
    - Curtis Lighting Inc. (Chicago), 1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 12)
      Includes three blueprints related to gallery lighting plans.
    - Dahlstrom Metallic Door Inc. (Jamestown, NY), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 13)
      Includes nine blueprints related to elevators.
    - Del Turco Brothers Inc. (Harrison, NJ), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 14)
      Includes about fifteen blueprints of plans concerning mosaic and terrazzo floor layouts.
    - Edwd. F. Caldwell & Co. Inc., 1938 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 12)
      Includes two drawings of light fixtures for the Assembly Room.
    - Federal Seaboard Terra Cotta Corp. (Perth Amboy, NJ), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 1)
      Includes three blueprints (initial and revision) of details of pieces.
    - Frank Scolaro Marble Co. (New York), 1938 (Drawer 9B-B4, Folder 1)
      Includes 32 blueprints of plans related to marble work throughout the building.
    - General Bronze Corp. (Long Island City), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B4, Folder 2)
      Includes 26 blueprints of plans of bronze work for windows, frames for glass brick, and window stools (plan #1 through 11).
    - General Bronze Corp. (Long Island City). Rolled Plan, 1937 (Roll 7, Folder -)
      In addition to the above plans, there is one rolled General Bronze plan. This is plan # 3, detail of bronze windows, with an approved date of 8/5/1937. A later version of plan 3, from October 1937, is in the above folder.
    - The Gorham Company, 1938 (Drawer 7A-B12, Folder 15)
      Includes a rejected sketch design for a cast bronze tablet memorializing Egbert Benson.
    - Hollerith, George, 1936-1937 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 11)
      Includes four blueprints of surveys.
    - J. J. Fisher Co. (Brooklyn), 1937 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 9)
      Includes blueprints of skylight details, plan #581 (4 sheets, multiple copies, some fragmented).
    - J. J. Fisher Co. (Brooklyn), 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 10)
      Includes blueprints of gutter lining, snowguard, louvre, and other roof and skylight details (plan #582, 584, 585, 589, 591, 593, 625, 627, and others without numbers due to fragmenting).
    - John L. Goss Corp. (Stonington, Maine), 1937 (Drawer 9B-B4, Folder 3)
      Includes 14 blueprints of plans related to granite work, including facing for the 76th and 77th Street wings, isolated sills and copings for the rear walls and roof, and sidewalk curbs.
    - M. T. Davidson Co. (Brooklyn), 1936 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 2)
      Includes one blueprint of a pump & receiver.
    - MacNutt, Watts & Tankard (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 3)
      Includes whiteprints and one blueprint related to electric work, including a schedule (six sheets, 2 copies).
    - Norton Lasier Co. (Chicago), 1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 4)
      Includes six blueprints related to floor closers.
    - Peelle Co. (Brooklyn), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 5)
      Includes five whiteprints of plans for manually-operated doors.
    - Quaker City Iron Works (Philadelphia), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 6)
      Includes two blueprints of a plan for a fire tank.
    - Snead & Co. (Jersey City, NJ), 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 7)
      Includes 36 blueprints of plans for the book stacks, including connections to structural steel, floor plans, stair and elevator layouts, work desks, enclosures, and columns. Also plans for office partitions.
    - Snead & Co. (Jersey City, NJ), 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B6, Folder 8)
      Includes 18 blueprints of plans for book stacks, including connections to structural steel, floor plans, stair and elevator layouts, sliding reference shelves, work desks, and enclosures.
    - Spencer, White & Prentis, 1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 7)
      Includes eight blueprints concerning piles, pile locations, and piers.
    - Sprague & Henwood (New York), 1936 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 8)
      Includes one whiteprint concerning borings.
    - Sprague & Henwood (New York), 1936 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 9)
      Includes two blueprints concerning borings.
    - Strawbridge & Clothier (New York), 1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 10)
      Includes two blueprints concerning the book stacks' tile floor.
    - Structural Contracting Corp. (Westbury, L.I.), 1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 11)
      Includes two blueprints of detail of window grilles and of skylight sub-sash for office of Mr. Winter.
    - Superior Steel Door and Trim Co. (College Point, NY), 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder -)
      This oversize flat box includes three sets of about fifty blueprints each of plans of doors, trim, etc.
    - Superior Steel Door and Trim Co. (College Point, NY), 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B4)
      Includes 16 blueprints of plans of doors, trim, frames, etc.
    - Taylor-Fichter Steel Construction Co. (New York), 1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 12)
      Includes six blueprints of plans concerning alterations to the 2nd floor mezzanine.
    - Trane Co. (La Crosse, Wis.), 1935-1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 13)
      Includes ten blueprints of plans for heating units, coil assembly, etc. One of the plans is missing a title box; the unfragmented version can be found in the Baker-Smith folders (drawing BS101).
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (1 of 4), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      This folder and the next three include many small blueprints of sketches made by Turner concerning details for doors, granite, wall slots, pits, and other matters. This first folder includes a partial inventory for sketches numbered 1 through 63. Not all the sketches recorded on the inventory are in the folders, and the final folder holds sketches not on the inventory. The original cover sheet for these sketches, also in this first folder, referred to these as "extra copies" of Turner sketches. In addition to the inventory, this first folder holds a schedule of interior wood jambs, a schedule of door trim, and sketches # 1 through 9.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (2 of 4), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Includes Turner sketches # 10 through 29.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (3 of 4), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Includes Turner sketches # 30 through 64.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (4 of 4), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Includes Turner sketches # A through U, with gaps.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (1 of 3), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      This folder and the next two include various small blueprints of sketches made by Turner. The original cover sheet, found in this first folder, referred to these as miscellaneous sketches. This first folder includes three plot plans drawn by Walker & Gillette, with Turner's related sketches attached to two of them.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (2 of 3), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Includes a schedule of interior wood jambs, a schedule of door trim, and a schedule of lintels by room.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York) (3 of 3), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Includes various sketches related to doors, granite, wood trim, lintel, skylight roof openings, and other details.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Includes several blueprints of Turner's sketches, most lettered from A through P, with some numbered (39, 39a, 49a, 51, and 52).
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York), 1938 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Includes two blueprints by Turner: drawing # 73A (detail of steps, assembly room) and drawing S1000 concerning the steps from the 1st mezzanine to book stack.
    - [Turner Construction Co. (New York)?], 1938 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Includes several blueprints of lists of hardware for doors.
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York), 1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 14)
      Includes a whiteprint List of Architectural & Misc Metals (2 sheets).
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 15)
      Includes 20 blueprints (4 sets) of schedules of wood trim and wood doors (plan # H101through H105).
    - Turner Construction Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 16)
      Includes 20 blueprints and two whiteprints of plans of various construction details.
    - [Turner Construction Co. (New York)?], 1937 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 17)
      Includes five plans on tracing paper, possibly prepared by Turner. Subjects include a sidewalk bridge, proposed plant layout, ductwork(?), and two details.
    - Various Subcontractors, 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 18)
      Includes blueprints from American Air Filter Co. (vent), Chesebro-Whitman Co. (tubular steel towers), Cornell Iron Works (tubular steel doors; two plans), Miller & Doing, Inc. (copper cheneau), Mosler Safe Co. (masonry), New York Steam Corp. (proposed 6" service), Snead & Co? (book stack arrangement), T.P. McLoughlin, Inc. (plumber's plan-stone tubs), and Whitney Duplicating Check Co. (coat room equipment layout).
    - Various Subcontractors, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Includes small blueprints concerning sump pumps by Quimby Pump Co. (Newark, NJ), Josam Manufacturing Co. (Michigan City, Ind.), and Cutler-Hammer Inc. (New York).
    - W. D. Allen Manufacturing Co. (New York), 1937-1938 (Drawer 7A-B13, Folder 19)
      Includes ten blueprints of plans concerning fire hose cabinets.
    - W. S. Tyler Co., 1937 (Drawer 9B-B4, Folder 4)
      Includes nine blueprints of plans concerning details of the three elevators.
    - Walker & Gillette List of Plans, [1938?] (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Includes cards listing plans by number and title. Though not noted as such, the bulk are Walker & Gillette plans, though at least one appears to refer to Sprague & Henwood's boring Plan (# 0-0). These can be helpful at further identifying the subject of the specific plans noted in the Walker & Gillette list that follows.
    - Walker & Gillette, 1936 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 1)
      Includes a blueprint (six sheets) of Walker & Gillette's "Scheme #1" and two other blueprints of sections and a plan of the reading room.
    - Walker & Gillette, 1936 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 2)
      Includes two sets of reproductions of Walker & Gillette's proposed floor plans of 1936, six sheets in each set, one a positive image, the other negative.
    - Walker & Gillette, [1936?] (Drawer 12A-B2, Folder 2)
      Includes schematic plans of the first and second floors on hard backing.
    - Walker & Gillette, [1937?] (Drawer 12A-B2, Folder 3)
      Includes three drawings of building design proposals, with the accepted one signed as approved by Director Alexander Wall.
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 3)
      Includes 13 blueprints of a north-south section for excavation, and floor plans for the basement and 1st floor (plan # 2 and 3).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 4)
      Includes eleven blueprints of the 2nd floor plan (plan # 4).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 5)
      Includes 13 blueprints of the 2nd floor mezzanine plan and revisions to the plan (plan # 5 and 5A.flap).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 6)
      Includes 21 blueprints of the 3rd floor plan, revision to the 3rd floor plan, and the attic floor plan (plan # 6, 6A, and 6A.flap).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 7)
      Includes 17 blueprints of the roof plan and the Central Park West elevation (plan # 7 and 8).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 8)
      Includes 20 blueprints of the 76th Street, 77th Street, and rear elevations (plan # 9, 10, and 11).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 9)
      Includes 16 blueprints of longitudinal section A-A and revision to the section (plan # 12 and 12A.flap).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 10)
      Includes 17 blueprints of cross section B-B, revision to the cross section, and longitudinal C-C (plan # 13.P3, 13A.flap, and 14).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 11)
      Includes 18 blueprints of details of existing stonework, exterior detail and wall section, typical book stack floor, southwest corridor plan, interior elevations, and revision to court elevation (plan # 15, 16, 17A, 18, 19, and 19A).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 12)
      Includes 34 blueprints of cross-sections, interior elevations, roof and skylights, typical stack wall treatment with ducts, and details of stairs (plan # 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26 (one copy attached to SK.104 and an associated letter from Walker & Gillette to Turner), 27, 28, and 29).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937 (Drawer 12A-B4, Folder 1)
      Includes a set of 15 blueprints, originally rolled together, that were issued to all trades on 2 June 1937. Plan # 5A. flap, 6A.flap, 10, 12A.flap, 13A.flap, 14, 16, 18, 19, 19A, 20, 23, 24, 26, and 28.
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 9B-B4, Folder 5)
      Includes 19 blueprints of elevations and details (some full scale) of Views of Old New York Room and Executive Committee Room, detail of paneling in director's room, location of wall registers, door trims and frames, and details of toilet rooms, locker room, kitchen, and elsewhere (plan # 30, 35, 41, 42, 43, 47, and 48).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B3, Folder 13)
      Includes 29 blueprints of corridors, wall sections, partitions, window grilles, etc. (plan # 31, 32, 33, 34, 36, 37, 38, and 39).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937 (Drawer 12A-B4, Folder 2)
      Includes ten blueprints of plans of schedules of doors; ceiling heights, furring, and registers; and skylights (plan # 40, 44, and 46).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937 (Drawer 12A-B4, Folder 3)
      Includes a whiteprint with original pencilling of the Specification Schedule of Material (plan #49, sheets 1, 2, 3, and 5).
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B4, Folder 4)
      Includes six sets (5 sheets each, one for each floor basement through third) of blueprints of the Specification Schedule of Material (plan #49) and a blueprint of a preliminary progress schedule.
    - Walker & Gillette, 1937-1938 (Drawer 12A-B4, Folder 5)